

Riasat Azim Khan

Game Programmer

CONTACT



+8801921534874



riasat2274@gmail.com



riasatazimkhan2274



<u>Portfolio</u>

EDUCATION



Engineering Degree in Computer Science North South University Dhaka Bangladesh 2011 - 2014

SKILLS

- Unity C#
- Game Programmer
- Debugging
- Particle System
- Shader Graph
- VersionControl
- **SDK** Implementation
- Optimisation
- Ad Monetisation
- In App Purchase
- Trello
- **Android Deployment**
- iOS Deployment

Published Titles

- Prank Master 3d
 - Core gameplay, Effects
 - Alpha Potato
 - Android and iOS
- Pawn Shop Master
 - Core gameplay Loop
 - Alpha Potato
 - Android and iOS

SUMMARY

I specialize in making 3d/2d games using the UNITY game engine. With experience over 10 years I focus not only on high quality games but also optimizing the development process.

I am Well acquainted with SDK deployments, Ad networks deployments, performance optimisation, custom shaders using shader graphs, HLSL and Particle effects.

I emphasize effective communications for better task management. I also love contributing to game design.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Senior Game Programmer

Studios

Jai

Kolpoverse
sameplay to production
s(From Core Gameplay to
S
ntation, Version control
2
Senior Game Progra

ammer

Alpha Potato

Feb 2020 - Dec 2022

☐ Quick prototyping for Hyper Casual games (From Core
Gameplay to production)
☐ Lighting, Shaders and effects
Optimization, SDK implementation, Version control

■ Worked on two published games

☐ Videos of my Projects



Game Programmer Pechas game Studios

Jan 2015 - Jan 2020

☐ Casual (From Core Gameplay to production)

effects on games (particle system etc)l